

Contact

Phone

+918469699889

Email

mayurahir1991@hotmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/mayur-myatra 27694b4b4

Address

Plot No.: 141/D, Ward: 4/B, Vandana Society, Rambag Road, Nr. BOI, Adipur, Kachchh, Gujarat, INDIA. - 370205

Skills

- Team Work
- Time Management
- Leadership
- Front end and Backend Developer
- Technical Skills
- Used Case Testing

Expertise

- Python
- MySQL
- Flask
- Node JS
- React JS
- REST APIs
- Tkinter
- Django

Language

- English
- Hindi
- Gujarati

Freelancer Projects (Currently Working on)

Account and Stock Management Software in Python with Flask APIs and React JS with MySQL Workbench and also working with Git.

Mayur Myatra

Python and React Developer

Skilled in information systems management, analysis, troubleshooting, documentation, system and program security, systems analysis, hardware and software installation, applications, and program management. - Management skills include the ability to Manage and motivate co-workers from all backgrounds, solution-oriented work style, decisive and confident decision-making, and in-depth proficiency with new technology trends. Well-developed communication skills demonstrated through fluency in English, Hindi, and Gujarati, and the ability to work well independently and as part of a team. Have experience as a freelancer also worked with APIs, Flask react js and javascript, and VB.net.

Experience

December 2014 - December 2015.

Acute Informatics Pvt Itd
 Desktop Support Engineer L1

Effectively handled Hardware, Laptop, All-in-One PC, Network, and Printer Basic Troubleshooting and Software SAP-related problems, Outlook Mail Configuration with Mail Troubleshooting, and PST and OST file-related problems as Desktop Support Engineer L1. (DL1).

November 2017 - February 2019

Freelance Work

(Apr 2017 - Feb 2018)

• creative info-links Pvt Ltd Customer Support Engineer

(Nov 2017 - Apr 2018)

Worked with a team of 100 employees in a busy Real Estate Company and FCI. Effectively handled Network and Printer Basic Troubleshooting and Stock Management portal-related problems Outlook Mail Configuration with Mail Troubleshooting, PST and OST file-related problems, Cameras related issues, DVR Troubleshooting, Router Troubleshooting and configuration, Firewall Handling, ERP Server related issues Handling, Server Troubleshooting as customer support engineer.

August 2019 - May 2024

• PC Solutions and Services (Aug 2019 - Dec 2020)

Developer/Customer Support Engineer

Magenta Connect Pvt Ltd

(Feb 2021 - May 2024)

Developer/Customer Success Manager

I have handled a team of 6 employees in a Software Company and other IT Companies, FARVISION ERP Software Related issues, ERP Server related issues Handling, Server Troubleshooting, Data Management, Data Sync, Integration Specialist, Handled, Business Intelligence Software, UI/UX Designer, React.js, Python Scripts, MYSQL, Team Leader, Software Testing and Used case Testing. In Current Company Data analytics, ETL, Data Visualizing. Works with different types of DBMS. I also worked with Python with Flask APIs and Django as well. I have experience with React JS, Javascript, and Rest API—Python, Node.js, etc.

Also, worked as a developer. I am also working on React JS, Flask, and My SQL and Django frameworks. I also have experience in git and AWS servers like S3 from my previous job. In my last job, I also worked with Python. I know data mining and data Manipulation with the Pandas, Numpy, Matplotlib, selenium, tkinter, library. I also handled multiple queries at a time. My total experience is 5 years. I worked with CRM Products as well

Business Intelligence software Project : I have created modules worked with Flask, ReactJS, My SQL, REST APIs, Pandas, Numpy, Tkinter etc.

Account and Stock Management Software Project: I have created modules worked with Flask, ReactJS, My SQL, REST APIs, Pandas, Numpy, Tkinter, Javascript, HTML, Axious APIs, Git S3, FC2 etc.

Education

MCA

Master of Computer Application

Year of Passing: 2020

University: SMU Distance Education

BCA

Bachelor of Computer Application

Year of Passing: 2013

University: K.S.K.V.K.U.

Reference

Mahendra Dahisaria

CEO,

PC Solutions & Ltd

Phone:

Email: mahendra@crestindia.in

Beena Panchal

Manager,

Acute Informatics Pvt Ltd

Phone:

Email: beena.panchal@acuteinformatics.in

Projects

Hotel Management software with MS Access database and VB.net software.

Travel Management Software with MS Access database and VB.net software. The database was MS access and Software Was made in VB.net.

MagentaBI Extractor with Python, Node.js, React JS. The Database was MySQL (Workbench) for the server also worked with AWS S3 Bucket. Libraries I have worked with Pandas, Numpy, Matplotlib, Selenium, tkinter, etc.

Account and Stock Management Software in Python with Flask APIs and React JS with MySQL Workbench and also working with Git.